A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Office of the Secretary of Finance, 1998-2005 (bulk 2002-2005)
Library of Virginia
- Series VII. Records, 2002-2005., Extent: 8.50 cubic feet. (Box 28-51)
  One other notable document is a communication document, ca. June 2003, Thematic Message Around Administration, 2003, describing the administration's philosophy, policy priorities, 2003 Work Plan and Communication Plan (B41, F9).
  - Summary of Capital Outlay Requests, 2006-2008, October 2005 (part one) (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Summary of Capital Outlay Requests, 2006-2008, October 2005 (part two) (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Summary of Capital Outlay Requests, 2006-2008, October 2005 (part three) (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Budget Development, 2006-2008, John M. Bennett, Secretary of Finance, November 2005 (part one) (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Budget Development, 2006-2008, John M. Bennett, Secretary of Finance, November 2005 (part two) (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Budget Development and Meetings with the Governor, November-December 2005 (part one) (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Budget Development and Meetings with the Governor, November-December 2005 (part two) (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Budget Development and Meetings with the Governor, November-December 2005 (part three) (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Department of Medical Assistance Services Issues, July 2003 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Community College System, Transfer Initiative Program, 2003 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources, Strategic Planning and Issues, 21 July 2003 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Technology, VITA, July 2003 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Public-Private Education Facilities and Infrastructure Act of 2002, 2002-2003 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Economic Growth and Tax Relief Reconciliation Act of 2001, Preliminary Analysis by Dept. of Taxation, 2001 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Financial Statements, 2003 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Receivables, Dept. of Taxation Compliance Overview, 27 May 2003 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - AMS Project Schedule, Dept. of Taxation, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Strategic Planning/Performance Measurements, 2003 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Communication Plan for Tax Reform Roll-out and Advocacy, October 2003 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Strategic Planning/Performance Measurements, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Budget Growth, FY 1997 to FY 2002 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Reengineering, Council on Virginia's Future, Group Meeting/Strategic planning materials, 2005 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Virginia Horse Center, 2005 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - New College of Virginia, 2005 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Group Life Insurance, 2003 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Efficiency/Effectiveness Initiative (Council on Virginia's Future), 2004 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Revenue Re-Forecast, 2004 Session, February 2004 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Employment Commission, Budget Decision Package for FY 2007/08, 2005 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Works, 2004 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Budget Preparation for 2006 General Assembly Session, 2005 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Proposed Tax Reform Plan, 2003-2004 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Norfolk Land Deal, 2005 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - BRAC Commission, Oceana, 2005 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Budget Initiatives for the 2006 General Assembly Session, 2005 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Letter/Documents to Governor Warner from Donald M. Itzkoff, 29 July 2005 re: tax credit bonds (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Article, 21st Century Workplace, 25 July 2005 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Rating Agency Visit (Moody's), September 2003 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Commercial Activities Inventory, 2005 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Energy Performance-Based Contracts, 2004 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Medicaid Forecast, 2003 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Medicaid Forecast, 2004 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - OCR Agreement (U.S. Dept. of Education, Office for Civil Rights Agreement, Virginia State University, 2005 Budget Request Summary) (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Telecommunications Taxation in Virginia, 2004 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Energy Policy, 2005 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Higher Education Model, Base Adequacy Model for Institutions of Higher Education, 2003 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Enterprise Applications PPEA Program Manager, 2005 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - NASCAR Hall of Fame, 2005 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - High Priority 2004-2006 Capital Outlay Projects, 2003 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Other Post Employment Benefits (OPEB), 2005 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - ERP Documents, 2004-2005 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Budget Issues (eVA and NASCAR Hall of Fame), 2005 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Virginia's Revenue Forecasting Process and Processes Used in Other States, 28 June 2005 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Virginia Employment Commission Budget Problems, 2005 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Estimated Fiscal Impact on Virginia of The Working Families Tax Relief At of 2004 and the American Jobs Creation Act of 2004, 15 November 2004 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Council on Virginia's Future, Best Managed State Sub-Group Planning Session, October 2003 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Virginia Economic Development Partnership (Dell, Project Emily), 2004 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Car Tax Forecast for FY 2003-2006, November 2002 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Year-End Balances, Summary Reports on General Fund and Lottery Revenue Collections, FY 2003, July 2003 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Governor's Advisory Board of Economics, Meeting Materials for 22 October 2003 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Jobs For Virginia (Rural Virginia Initiatives), 2004 (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts, Report on Governor's Office, 2004 (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - Virginia Modeling and Simulation Initiative, 2005 (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - Virginia Arts and Culture Economic Growth Coalition, 2004-2005 (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - Rainy Day Fund, 2004 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Title IV-E Liability, FY 2005 Federal Cash Shortfall, 2005 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - The Six-Year Financial Plan, Based on HB 1500/SB 700, Dept. of Planning and Budget, January 2005 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Six-Year Plan, 2005 Session (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - General Fund Financial Plan, Fiscal Years 2005-10, Revised Revenues, 2005 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Revenue Re-Forecast, February 2002 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Interim Revenue Forecasts, July and August 2002 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Revenue Forecasts, Fall 2004 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Approved Reconvened Amendments, 2005 (part one) (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Approved Reconvened Amendments, 2005 (part two) (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Building Virginia's Future: A Capital Improvement Plan, 29 January 2002 (part one) (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Building Virginia's Future: A Capital Improvement Plan, 29 January 2002 (part two) (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Dept. of Planning and Budget, 2003 Budget Development, December 2002 (part one) (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Dept. of Planning and Budget, 2003 Budget Development, December 2002 (part two) (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Dept. of Planning and Budget, 2003 Session of the General Assembly, Enrolled Budget Bill Review, February 2003 (part one) (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Dept. of Planning and Budget, 2003 Session of the General Assembly, Enrolled Budget Bill Review, February 2003 (part two) (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Background Information, Budget Development, Miscellaneous Documents, Fall 2002 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Interest and Literary Fund Forecasts, November 2002 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Public Education Funding Conference Committee Report on HB 30, 9 March 2002 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Baseball Stadium Authority, 2004 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Capital Outlay Plans, 2003 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Agency Processes, Strategic Planning Initiatives, 2003 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Governor's Amendments, Fiscal Outlook 2003 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Dept. of Medical Assistance Services, Medicaid Recoveries and Revenue Maximization Efforts, 2003 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - General Obligation Bonds, Meeting, 22 September 2002 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - NASCAR Hall of Fame, 2005 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Virginia Dept. of Planning and Budget, Economic Analysis of Governor Warner's Budget and Tax Reform Plan, 7 January 2004 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Car Tax Issues, March 2002 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Dept. of Corrections, Budget Issues, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Office of the Attorney General, Budget Issues, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Dept. of the State Internal Auditor, Budget Issues, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Recommended Candidates for The Governor's Advisory Board of Economist and The Governor's Advisory Council on Revenue Estimates, 29 April 2002 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Congressional Delegation Meeting with Governor Mark Warner and Cabinet, 18 March 2002 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Governor Mark Warner's Education Funding Proposals (School Construction), 2002 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Cabinet Retreat, 5-6 May 2002 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Virginia Performing Arts Center, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Virginia Bioinformatics Institute, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Eastern Virginia Medical School, Medical Sciences Complex, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - State Employee Health Insurance, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Budget Conference Letters, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Car Tax, FY 2002 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Emergency Medical Services Funding (Two-for-Life), 2002 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Virginia Commonwealth University Health Systems (VCUHS), 2002 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Smithsonian Institute, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - 2003 Aviation World's Fair, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Tobacco Commission, 2002-2003 (part one) (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Tobacco Commission, 2002-2003 (part two) (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Route 28 Project Financing, 2002 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Transportation Authority/Referendum Issues, 2002 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Center for the Performing Arts, 2002 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Privatizing ABC, 2002 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - VAR Forecast, 31 January 2002 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Advanced Shipbuilding and Carrier Integration System, 2002 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Agency Head Agreements, Finance Secretariat, 2002 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Tax Restructuring, Internal Working Group, 2002 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Cabinet Workgroup on Budget Development and Governmental Restructuring, 2002-2003 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - SB 668 (02) Hampton Roads Transportation District Program (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Anti-Terrorism Grants Tracking Issues, 2002 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Technology Strategic Plan, 2002 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Federal and Out-of-State Inmate Contracts, 2002 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Senate Finance Committee presentation by Secretary Bennett, 13 June 2002 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Agency Reduction Strategies, 15 October 2002 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - General Fund Budget Shortfall, 20 November 2002 (part one) (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - General Fund Budget Shortfall, 20 November 2002 (part two) (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Conference Report on House Bill 1400 (Budget Bill), March 2003 (part one) (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Conference Report on House Bill 1400 (Budget Bill), March 2003 (part two) (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Conference Report on House Bill 1400 (Budget Bill), March 2003 (part three) (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Budget Concerns, 2004 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - FY 2002 Budget Materials (including Conference Report/Summary on HB 30), 2002 (part one) (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - FY 2002 Budget Materials (including Conference Report/Summary on HB 30), 2002 (part two) (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - FY 2002 Budget Materials (including Conference Report/Summary on HB 30), 2002 (part three) (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - STARS Management Group Meeting, 28 March 2003 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Tax Refund Letters, 2001 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Car Tax Triggers, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Tax Replacement Project (Becky's Project), 2002 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Fixed Date Conformity, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Estate Tax, 2003 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Sales and Use Tax Acceleration, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Sales and Use Tax Exemptions, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Streamlined Sales Tax Project, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Department of Taxation Issues, 2002-2003 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Constitutional Officer Liability Program, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Insurance, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Debt Materials, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Treasury Board, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Division of Unclaimed Property, 2002-2003 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Bond Proceeds for Bureau of Capital Outlay Management (BCOM), 2002 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Department of the Treasury, Generic, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Revenue Reports, 2002 and 2004 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Revenue, Fiscal Year 2002, 2001 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Hampton Roads Transportation Referendum, 2002 (part one) (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Hampton Roads Transportation Referendum, 2002 (part two) (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Department of Motor Vehicles, Audit, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Transportation, 2004 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Litter Control and Recycling Fund, 2003-2004 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Virginia Department of Taxation, VA Tax and AMS Partnership Project, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Strategic Message Around Administration, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Governor's Advisory Board of Economists, Recommendations, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Virginia Retirement System, Group Life Insurance, 2001-2002 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Governor's Initiatives, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Federal Aid to Virginia, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Veto Options, Budget, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Budget Material, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Global Insight, 2002-2003 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Governor Warner's Tax Reform Plan for Virginia, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - General Provisions Language, Appropriation Act, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Aviation Budget, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Department of Corrections, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Virginia State Police Compensation Issues, 2002-2003 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Virginia State Police Retention Plan, 2003 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Direct Aid to Public Education, 2003 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Prepaid Education Program, 2003 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Decentralization of Higher Education, 2002 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - OB/GYN DMAS Reimbursement, 2004 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Medicaid Dental Services Reimbursement Rates, 2003-2004 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Executive Branch Strategic Planning, Service Area Planning, and Performance Based Budgeting for FY 2006-08, 2005 (part one) (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Executive Branch Strategic Planning, Service Area Planning, and Performance Based Budgeting for FY 2006-08, 2005 (part two) (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Council on Virginia's Future, Council Planning Group, 4 August 2005 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Council on Virginia's Future, Retreat, 29 August 2005 (part one) (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Council on Virginia's Future, Retreat, 29 August 2005 (part two) (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Council on Virginia's Future, Meeting Documents, 2005 (part one) (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Council on Virginia's Future, Meeting Documents, 2005 (part two) (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Council on Virginia's Future, Meeting Documents, 2005 (part three) (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Council on Virginia's Future, Meeting Documents, 2005 (part four) (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - 2003 Proposed Legislation of the Finance Secretariat (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - 2004 Proposed Legislation of the Finance Secretariat (part one) (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - 2004 Proposed Legislation of the Finance Secretariat (part two) (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Finance Secretariat Proposed Legislation, 2005 Session, 9 September 2004 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Finance Secretariat Proposed Legislation, 2005 Session, 17 January 2005 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Budget Development, 2005 Session, November-December 2004 (part one) (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Budget Development, 2005 Session, November-December 2004 (part two) (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Interim Meeting of The Governor's Advisory Board of Economists, 11 July 2002 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - The Economic Outlook, prepared by the Virginia Department of Taxation for Review by the Governor's Advisory Board of Economists, 22 October 2002 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - The Economic Outlook, prepared by the Virginia Department of Taxation for Review by the Governor's Advisory Board of Economists, 22 October 2003 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - The Economic Outlook, prepared by the Virginia Department of Taxation for Review by the Governor's Advisory Board of Economists, 20 October 2004 (copy one) (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - The Economic Outlook, prepared by the Virginia Department of Taxation for Review by the Governor's Advisory Board of Economists, 20 October 2004 (copy two) (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Meeting of the Governor's Advisory Board of Economists, 20 October 2004 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - The Economic Outlook, prepared by the Virginia Department of Taxation for Review by the Governor's Advisory Board of Economists, 24 October 2005 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Meeting of the Governor's Advisory Board of Economists, 24 October 2005 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Meeting of the Governor's Advisory Council on Revenue Estimates, 7 August 2002 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Meeting of the Governor's Advisory Council on Revenue Estimates, 22 October 2002 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - The Economic Outlook and Revenue Forecast Through Fiscal Year 2006 prepared by the Virginia Department of Taxation for Review by the Governor's Advisory Council on Revenue Estimates, 25 November 2002 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Meeting of the Governor's Advisory Council on Revenue Estimates, 25 November 2002 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - The Economic Outlook and Revenue Forecast Through Fiscal Year 2006 prepared by the Virginia Department of Taxation for Review by the Governor's Advisory Council on Revenue Estimates, 21 November 2003 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Meeting of the Governor's Advisory Council on Revenue Estimates, 21 November 2003 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - The Economic Outlook and Revenue Forecast Through Fiscal Year 2008 prepared by the Virginia Department of Taxation for Review by the Governor's Advisory Council on Revenue Estimates, 22 November 2004 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Meeting of the Governor's Advisory Council on Revenue Estimates, 22 November 2004 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - The Economic Outlook and Revenue Forecast Through Fiscal Year 2008 prepared by the Virginia Department of Taxation for Review by the Governor's Advisory Council on Revenue Estimates, 21 November 2005 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Meeting of the Governor's Advisory Council on Revenue Estimates, 21 November 2005 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Budget Reform, 2002, 2004 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Car Tax Cap, 2004 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Virginia Issues, Reforming the Individual Income Tax, by John H. Bowman, VCU, 2002 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Tax Restructuring (Governor's Tax Restructuring Working Group), 2003 (part one) (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Tax Restructuring (Governor's Tax Restructuring Working Group), 2003 (part two) (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Tax Restructuring (Governor's Tax Restructuring Working Group), 2003 (part three) (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Proposed Changed in Income Tax Structure on Resident Tax Payers (Governor's Tax Restructuring Working Group), 2003 (part one) (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Proposed Changed in Income Tax Structure on Resident Tax Payers (Governor's Tax Restructuring Working Group), 2003 (part two) (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Proposed Changed in Income Tax Structure on Resident Tax Payers (Governor's Tax Restructuring Working Group), 2003 (part three) (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Tax Restructuring (Governor's Tax Restructuring Working Group), Agenda Items, 10 July 2003 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Tax Restructuring (Governor's Tax Restructuring Working Group), Agenda Items, 23 July 2003 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Tax Restructuring (Governor's Tax Restructuring Working Group), Agenda Items, 30 July 2003 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Tax Restructuring (Governor's Tax Restructuring Working Group), Agenda Items, 22 August 2003 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Governor's Tax Restructuring Working Group, Comparing the Virginia Individual Income Tax to Other States, 17 September 2003 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Governor's Tax Restructuring Working Group, Package Spreadsheet, November 2003 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Governor's Tax Restructuring Working Group, Profile of Tax Returns for All Residents, 2003 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Governor's Tax Restructuring Working Group, Other States, 2003 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Governor's Tax Restructuring Working Group, Closing Corporate Loopholes, 13 November 2003 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Revenue Re-Forecast, October-December 2003 and February 2004 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Military Family Tax Relief Act of 2003, 18 November 2003 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Higher Education Budget Meeting, 19 November 2003 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Senator Chichester Tax Plan, 20 February 2004 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Potential General Fund Resources, April 2004 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Stopgap Budget, FY04 (HB 5008) (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Sales Tax Exemptions, HB 1448, 2004 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Local Option Sales Tax, FY 2005 Distribution (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Six Year Budget Projects, FY04-FY10, December 2003 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - House and Senate, Six Year Financial Plans, February 2005 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Delaware Holding Company (HB 5018), 2004 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - PPEA Due Diligent Project, 2005 Estimated Information Technology Budget, 30 March 2005 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - A Comparison of Effective Tax Rates at Various Income Levels for Selected States, Tax Year 2000, nd (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Governor's Tax Restructuring Working Group Briefing Binder for Secretary Bennett, Fall 2003 (part one) (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Governor's Tax Restructuring Working Group Briefing Binder for Secretary Bennett, Fall 2003 (part two) (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Governor's Tax Restructuring Working Group Briefing Binder for Secretary Bennett, Fall 2003 (part three) (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Governor's Tax Restructuring Working Group Briefing Binder, Fall 2003 (copy)(part one) (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Tax Reform Plan, Locality by Locality Data, ca. 2003 (part one) (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Tax Reform Plan, Locality by Locality Data, ca. 2003 (part two) (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Tax Reform Plan, Locality by Locality Data, ca. 2003 (part three) (Box 51, Folder 5)